Good morning. You're watching the
program with Ted R and John Kuryaku for
Monday, November 10th, 2025. Good
morning, John.
>> Good morning, Ted. How are you?
>> I'm good, but maybe not quite as good as
Gizlain Maxwell. The news just broke
about a minute ago that uh a
whistleblower exposed that uh she has
asked Trump to commute her sentence and
that prison employees say she's
receiving quote unquote concierge style
treatment.
You know, man, this is bad. This is bad.
Rudy Giuliani was just uh pardoned
early this morning and uh all these
other criminals who uh had something to
do with with um
denying uh the 2020 election. This is
I don't know.
>> And meanwhile, here you sit
>> waiting by the phone
>> quite literally. I listen I don't want
to get ahead of myself but I had I had
coffee on Friday evening
with
I had coffee Friday evening with a
cabinet member
>> and
he told me to be patient and I said it's
only because you're saying that that I
will be patient
but uh
>> you've been patient. I've been very
patient and um
>> it's November.
>> I don't know, man. I have to watch what
I say, which is another thing he told
me.
>> Yes.
>> But um
>> and we're we all understand that.
>> And I appreciate it, but I I have to say
that I'm not I'm not sanguin that that
this is all based on justice.
No, I mean, you know, let's face it, the
the the pardon uh right is something
that goes back to monarchy and we
inherited from that. So, it's not
really, you know, it's not really a
democratic small d democratic process.
Um,
>> well,
>> no. So, and well, you know, we're
crossing our fingers and obviously we,
like I said, I'll reiterate that we all
understand there are things you can't
talk about and shouldn't talk about. So,
uh, you know, we all want you to to get
we want that to come through.
>> And, you know, Ted, really for me, the
bottom line is there is literally
nothing else that I can do to make a
strong case. There's nothing. I've done
it. I've done it all. I've I've been on
every show I needed to go on. I've said
all the things I need to say. There's
nothing else I can do.
>> No, I I would I would say that's
probably true. I mean, you know, it's it
drives me a little crazy because when I
hear about like this morning when I
heard about the pardon when I woke up, I
was like, "Oh, blanket pardon. Maybe
John can be under the big blanket."
>> I actually read the article. It was the
first thing that I woke up to this
morning. I read the article thinking,
"Well, Giuliani is the headliner name.
Maybe I'm buried somewhere in the
bottom." Because often times what Trump
does, unlike what other uh presidents
have done, he'll pardon someone and not
tell anybody.
And they read about it in the press
like this Binance guy.
>> So bizarre.
>> This Binance guy said over the weekend,
Ted,
>> that he never met Donald Trump. He never
asked for a pardon. He never even
applied for a pardon.
>> Wow.
>> And Trump pardoned him anyway.
>> Yeah, that's that it's so it's so weird
and quirky. Um well, we got a lot to
talk about and hopefully one of these
mornings we're going to have your pardon
to talk about. And I hope so. Don't
forget about the show when you're taking
all those calls. Um because it would be
easy to be distracted. I always think
the worst thing and this is like my
warning to you. Make sure you stay
healthy because uh there was a guy I
don't know if you remember him maybe
about 20 years ago and he lived in New
York City. I think he might have been at
Colombia but he could have been at like
Brooklyn Polytech. I want to say
Brooklyn Polytech but he won he got the
call from Stockholm that he had won the
Nobel Prize in possibly physics um or
biochemistry. Anyway, he he he he he's a
Yale professor. He gets into his car to
drive up the Connecticut Turnpike to uh
to to up to uh New Haven and on route he
has a [__] heart attack, crashes his
car and dies.
>> Oh my god, that's
>> And it was like obviously he was so like
incredibly excited and overwhelmed it
killed him.
>> So [laughter] he got a So yoga. Well, I
may if if I get a pardon, I may take
that day off so I can go buy guns,
which I promised myself is the first
thing I'm going to do.
>> You're gonna Well, at least John Kuryaku
is stimulating the economy. [laughter]
Um, you know, even if even if even if
consumer spending is starting to slow
down a little bit. All right, let's go
ahead and and talk about what we're
going to be talking about, among other
things. And as usual, we always love to
get uh the questions and comments in the
Rumble and the YouTube live chats. Much
appreciated. All right, so obviously the
big news of the day is what appears to
be the shaping the formation of a deal.
Possibly it's really a deal uh related
to the shutdown. We'll get into that.
Um, also there's this pardon that we
just alluded to uh for 77 Trump um
affiliates including Giuliani, Sydney
Powell, Mark Meadows and so on. Uh these
this was all related to the 2020 um you
know efforts to overturn the the results
of the 2020 election. Um also super
interesting story about the Nordstream
the German investigation into the
Nordstream pipeline explosion. Um, I'm
it's almost starting to make me doubt my
doubt, but we should get into that.
John, what are you interested in talking
about first?
>> Well, to tell you the truth, if you
don't mind spending five minutes, I want
to talk about something that I posted on
Facebook um day before yesterday from
the Blaze.
Literally, nobody else has picked this
story up. But the Blaze is reporting
that the FBI has zeroed in on the
January 6th pipe bomber. That is that
person seen in security footage placing
pipe bombs in front of the RNC and the
DNC.
>> Mhm.
>> And that person is a Capitol police
officer who had been on rotation to the
CIA doing physical security. Now, this
is a female uh Capitol police officer,
now former Capitol police officer who
was injured in college
um in college sports and so has a limp
and they were able to to deduce from her
limp
um that she was the the bomber. Now,
when the Blaze sent a reporter over to
her house just to take a look at it,
they saw immediately that the house is
under surveillance, and that
surveillance is likely the FBI. Now, the
the blaze was very clear that this woman
has not been charged with a crime.
>> She has not had this case turned over to
a grand jury for indictment.
They just have used this technology to
determine that it is likely her. And
they put that likelihood at 94%.
>> That's very precise.
>> It's very precise and I think they did
it, you know, using computers. Um but
but uh this is a story to watch because
if it's true,
>> it adds a whole new layer to January
6th.
>> Well, how so? um could delve into that a
little bit
>> because then if if it's true that it was
her, did she do it on behalf of the CIA
or did the CIA know she was doing it
even if she was acting independently? Um
was this some kind of a a task from the
Capitol police? Was it a Was she a rogue
that had infiltrated the Capitol police
and then asked for a C a CIA transfer? I
mean, who who was doing what in this in
this situation? We we don't know
anything.
It does in the weasel words of
newspapers raise questions, doesn't it?
>> Yeah, indeed.
>> Um, so by the way, I I before we uh get
full on into today's show, I really want
to uh do a little housekeeping. Please
like, follow, and share the show. We
appreciate it. Um, we are going to be
here tomorrow, even though we sometimes
take federal holiday, we usually take
federal holidays off, but tomorrow is
Veterans Day. And no disrespect to the
veterans, but we will be here uh
tomorrow morning at 9:00 Eastern as
usual and throughout the rest of the
week. Also, we really want to uh send a
big D program thank you. Uh we did
achieve the $1,000 goal for Robbie aid.
So Robbie is Robbie's fully funded uh
between you guys and you know, you're
welcome to contribute if you'd like to.
Uh here's the URL again if you're
interested. uh you know there's nothing
wrong with with uh sending more if you
want. Givego.comwestglacaming
is the URL. I'll leave it up there for a
sec. Um but uh you know but basically
he's funded for no the month of
November. We will be back on December
1st bugging you again. But basically the
goal here is uh you guys pay a thousand
and uh John and I each pay 250 and uh we
have a producer and John and Robbie will
be back full-time with us after his
notice is over. He's on beginning week
two of his twoe notice at his current
employer from which he got doxed uh next
Monday on Monday, November 17th. So
you're going to want to be here for
that. Um and I'm sure Rody will pop in
from time to time as he is want to do.
Um anyway, thank you again for your
incredible generosity and we really
appreciate you guys and your support is
incredible.
>> Okay, so that's a story to watch. All
right, let's I think we should talk
about the shutdown deal. What do you
think?
>> Without a doubt.
>> Okay, so
>> you called it. You called it, Ted. I
mean, we said it last week. The
Democrats were weak and they were going
to cave and they caved. And for those of
us who are dependent on Obamacare, we
all got screwed today. That's I'm one of
them. Um yeah, and that is a uh so yeah,
so basically we have eight traders
including Tim Kaine from whom I really
expected more.
>> Angus King from which I expect nothing.
No.
>> Um and uh and and you know and and a
bunch and a half dozen others.
>> But both of New Hampshire's senators, I
expected much more from them.
>> Yeah.
>> Jean Shaheen and Maggie Hassan.
So disappointing.
>> Very disappointing. Maggie Hassan in
particular. Um, yeah, I have a personal
connection there that I'm not going to
get into, but uh, yeah, really really
annoying to to as as hell. Um, and uh,
and so yeah, so basically there's a lot
of mixed reporting here about how
important this vote is. Uh, does this I
mean I'm seeing everything, John, from
this is the floodgates have opened. Um,
this will be this means the shutdown is
coming to an end. there's nothing
Democrats can do. Obviously, they can't
do anything in the House. Um the
Republicans control both h both both
both houses. Um but there's also
reporting saying no, no, no, no. It's
not done yet. Um you know, there has to
be a few more votes. This is just a
procedural vote. [clears throat] Um it
doesn't mean that you get to the 60
filibuster vixie vote filibuster
breaking um supermajority,
>> right?
>> Um you know, so it's it's a little
confusing. Um and also so basically this
deal says that uh we get a we get an
extension through January 30th. So f the
government is funded for a quarter. Um
Democrats don't seem to have gotten
anything. They seem to have gotten
rolled here. I mean basically
retroactive pay uh for the people who've
been furled. They would have gotten that
anyway. Yeah. 1 million%. That's the
law. I mean no matter what Trump says,
right? um restoring SNAP and veteran
affairs benefits. Okay. I mean that's
good obviously. Um but all they're going
to get is a vote on the principal issue
at hand here, which is the Affordable
Care Act subsidies and tax breaks. Um
they're not going to get a guaranteed
support for it. They're going to get a
vote and the Republicans will just vote
no. Um so if they even get a vote,
right? I mean, so this is about maybe
getting Republicans on the record as
being against the Affordable Care Act
before the midterms. I mean, this seems
like it does really seem like a
surrender. Hakeem Jeff is actually
expressed, you know, displayed emotion
of actual anger and and uh seems to be
actually annoyed, something we don't
normally see, but there's nothing he can
do about it over in the House of
Representatives, you know. I mean the
house is the house is controlled by the
GOP.
>> What now?
>> That's exactly right. Well, you this is
an interesting thing.
>> So this deal this deal that may or may
not be on the table today um is not what
the House passed. And remember the idea
was the House passed the Trump budget
period and then they went into recess
and everybody went home. So the House
hasn't been in session for a month.
There's nobody on Capitol Hill. There
was an article in today's Washington
Post saying businesses are going
bankrupt because there's nobody on
Capitol Hill between the shutdown and
the recess. Okay. So,
the Senate then has come up with its own
agreement. That means that the House is
going to have to come back and vote on
the Senate version, which is exactly the
opposite of what they wanted to do. They
wanted to pass the House version and
then the Senate votes on the House
version. Now it's reversed. Well, Hakee
Jeff said last night that he can
[clears throat] he can speak for
literally every Democratic vote in the
House and every single Democrat will
vote no on the
budget that comes out of the Senate.
Well, the the Republicans need seven
Democratic senators to pass this thing.
The House needs only
three Republican congressmen to kill it.
So I'm wondering now if attention should
shift to the House because this is not
what Mike Johnson said he was going to
pass.
>> So basically confusion reigns and and
confusion is the best hope of people who
still want to have governmentbacked
insurance. And I'll tell you what, if if
people if people don't really know how
government works, you know, sixth grade
physics, ninth grade physics, physics,
uh, civics was a long time ago.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, watch this. This is how the sausage
is made. And it it's it's not pretty.
>> No, it really isn't. Um, it's bizarre.
Um,
>> yeah. Okay. So, um I mean, so I think
this is a really bad look for Democrats.
Let's let's do some analysis here. I
mean, what exactly is up with the Senate
caucus? I mean, Sen uh you know, Schumer
is the minority leader. He's the boss of
the Democrats in the Senate. He told
them all to vote no. He's voting no.
>> Yeah.
>> Personally, how come he couldn't keep
his his caucus in line?
>> That's that's a great question. And the
reason is because with a wink and a nod
last night, he said, "Well, I'm going to
vote against it, but you vote the way
you want to vote." So that's not
whipping votes. You know, there there's
a majority whip and a minority whip
because in the olden days, in the 1700s
and the 1800s, they used this figurative
whip to to get people to vote the way
leadership wanted them to vote. So, it's
become formalized in the position of
minority and majority whip. Schumer did
not whip votes last night. He told them
to vote their conscience, which is very
dangerous. That is a concession that
you've lost.
>> Yeah. So just go ahead and vote any way
you you want to vote 99.9%
of the time. And I mean this quite
literally. Votes are whipped. Nobody is
free to vote their conscience. That's
that's the duopoly that we have.
>> John, I don't understand though. Um like
so just last week I mean I know it's
like you know sort of like Winston Smith
in 1984. you start to question your own
memory. But if memory serves, less than
a week ago, Democrats just won a
stunning series of victories
>> in these off-year elections.
>> And everyone was saying like, and then
we had uh a lot of uh you know, hand
ringing on the part of Republicans, some
of whom are very smart, analytical
Republicans who said, "We're about to
get our clocks cleaned in the midterms
next November. We're we're in deep [__]
Uh the economy is making some uh there's
some warning blinking light blinking
warning lights right now. I mean, you
know, if you're the Democrats, you're
winning. We talked about how the
Democrats have a had a have a
predelection for, you know, snatching
defeat from the jaws of victory. But
still, even by those standards, this is
kind of stunning, isn't it? Right. I
mean, you guys kept this this this
shutdown going for over a month,
>> and you're literally not going to get
[__] out of it because eight douchebags
decided to cross over.
>> That is
Yeah, that is exactly what's wrong with
the Democratic party. They took their
wins from Tuesday and they said, "Aha,
the most important thing was that we won
on Tuesday and we flipped a couple of
state legislatures and we won a bunch of
school boards and we won in Republican
seats in Pennsylvania that no Democrat
had ever won before. We don't really
care about helping people with this ACA
situation, so we're just going to take
our wins and go home." And that's what
they're doing because they don't care
about people like you and me, Ted. They
don't care if we can't afford our health
care policies.
>> No, they they really don't. Um I think
they're understating the the the point,
too, when they say so there's 42 million
Americans who receive these subsidies,
right? They're saying [clears throat]
they're expecting between two and four
million people not to renew. I call
[__] on that. I think it's going to
be a lot more. I mean, when you go from,
you know, the subsidies are going up
well over 100% for the average person,
and in many cases, it's it's, you know,
it's a bell curve. In some cases, it'll
only go up a little bit, but in other
cases, it's going to go up a whole [__]
ton. Um, it's going to triple or
quadruple. Those triple or quadruple
people are not renewing. Um, you know,
especially if they're like under 60 and
they're like, you know, I'll just I'll
derp through this.
>> Exactly. Exactly. This is Listen, if
you're if you're a Democrat, this is
bad. If you're a Republican, it's still
bad. That's what this comes down to.
>> Yeah. It's going to be a hate off.
>> Yes.
>> Next next in the midterms. And I guess
the question is, will the will the
midterms be nationalized? I don't know.
They they rarely are.
>> Rarely. Rarely.
>> 94 74.
>> Yeah.
>> 82. 94 [clears throat]
74 80
um
>> 82, right?
>> 82 64 only because Kennedy had been
killed.
>> Yeah. Yep. So bizarre. Um
>> Yep.
>> Okay. So yeah, I don't know what's I
don't know where we go from here. I
mean, the whole thing is um it's very
very strange. Um, MA the cat says, "I
think they're just putting up resistance
for show while the corporate over
overlords commanded them to surrender."
Um, John, do you think this was about
the the flight delays? Um, you know,
you're hearing Democrats say like, well,
they were really freaking out over the
idea that they were they might get
blamed for the for, you know, the the
meltdown of the air traffic control
system. We have an average, we already
yesterday there were over 2,000 flight
cancellations. Yeah, we all know about
the fly. you know about the Ripple and
and uh yeah and you know the funny thing
too is at least according to the to the
New York Times um we've actually been
saved from more cancellations because I
didn't know this one of the lightest
travel periods is um is the first two
weeks of November because people are
waiting until Thanksgiving to do their
travel.
>> Yeah, John, this is actually a really
good time for future reference. This is
a great time. We're ending a great time
to travel. Like October 15th to November
15th.
>> Yeah.
>> I once flew to Beijing round trip from
Detroit. From New York via Detroit to
Beijing on Northwest
>> for 400 bucks.
>> Are you kidding me?
>> Granted, it was coach.
>> Yeah. But still, that's that's pretty
incredible.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's a great time of
the year. January is also another great
time of the year. January
>> January is a great time.
>> Like to like February 8th or so.
>> Yeah. Um, you know, you can go anywhere.
It costs nothing. And the weather's
often not as shitty as you think
wherever you go. Like, you know, it's
France. How bad could it be? It'll be
drizzling. It'll be 43. It's still
France.
>> The quason are still good.
>> Um, but I mean, so what happens now? I
mean, to me, I'm thinking about like
even if the Democrats don't care about
us, which I 100 million% agree with you.
You're right. They don't care. But the
thing is the weakness that it that it
conveys. I mean, it's like, why vote for
them, right? I mean, it's kind of like
you're winning and you throw away your
you're you're you know, all the polls
showed that the Republicans were getting
their clocks cleaned uh in the in this
in the in public opinion because of the
shutdown. Now, Democrats role, and I
know Schumer is probably really
frustrated. It's like, well, we've got
these eight [__] but were these
eight [__] offered anything? I mean,
we they they're only get I mean, I don't
even understand. You got to help me with
this. You're being promised a vote.
You're being promised a vote that you're
going to lose because of the numbers in
the House and the Senate. Why do you
want this promise? Yeah.
>> Why do you like And by the way, will you
get that vote? Is this just about
getting Republicans on the record uh
voting voting against the subsidies so
that maybe if they have the balls in
October next year, Democratic uh
Democrats running for reelection or
election can say, you know, Senator John
John Smith voted against American
healthcare. This little girl died as a
result.
>> Probably John Smith hates you.
>> Yeah, that's that's probably what we're
talking about here.
>> That's all it is.
>> I think so. It's all politics. They
don't care about us. That's the bottom
line. I mean, I can count on one hand
the number of senators that I think
truly care about the American people.
Well, I can count on one finger. I think
it's Bernie Sanders. I really do.
>> Yeah, he does care.
Um, someone's asking, Real Real is
asking me, but what year was that, Ted?
Um, I don't know what you're talking
about. Real Real, please clarify. Um,
so
yeah, I don't know. It's it's really
crazy. Um, looking up transhumanist
politicians by state shows you clearly
who works for the WEF, people like Dan
Krenshaw, Pete Buddha.
>> Oh, don't get me started on Crenshaw. Oh
my god.
>> Trump, Tulsi Gabbard, etc.
Krenshaw is one of those scumbags that
is in a is in a league all of his own.
You know what? Let me tell you about
Crenshaw.
So,
I briefly dated this woman
who
was considerably younger than I, very,
very attractive,
a leader in her field.
And uh we were at her place watching a
movie one night and it was about
midnight and her phone was on the floor
near me.
So midnight and the phone buzzes. She
gets a text message. It's from [__]
Crenshaw. And he says, "What are you
wearing?"
And I'm like, "It's I said it's Dan
Crenshaw." He says, "What are you
wearing?" and she says, "Oh, that that
[__] won't leave me alone."
So, um,
so I I took the phone and I wrote back.
I said, "Crenchaw, this is her
boyfriend. Why don't you ask your wife
what she's wearing?"
And he texts back, "Sorry,
scumbag."
His wife just had they had a 10-month
old baby at the time, but he's asking my
girlfriend what she's wearing at 12:00
at night. And then and then she she me
some of his other text messages. They
were filthy.
>> They were filthy. And she saved them
just in case she needed to use them
against him.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> Yeah, he's a scumbag.
>> Insane. Uh Soden 2324. Thank you so much
for the 1999 uh donation. Good morning,
guys. Hope all is well. [__] this
shutdown. My mom was stuck on on a on a
plane in Norfolk for four hours, then
the flight was cancelled. We're better.
Uh, we're better. We are way better than
than this. Yeah. Well, that's un
undeniably it's it's ridiculous. I mean,
if we were Molly and we had no money,
but we're literally pretending tying
tying our our hands behind our our
budgetary hands behind our backs and
pretending like we have no money. Um,
uh, also thanks for the five bucks for
real lump and proletariat. Uh, great
show. Can you have a URL in your
description to directly send you and
Robbie donations? Don't these platforms
take huge percent of contributions? Um,
yeah. Uh, the you can I'm going to put
up the PayPal link. That's the most
direct. I know they take part of it, but
it's not nearly as much as some of the
others. Uh, dprogram podcast atgmail is
the is the PayPal um donation button.
And I'll try to find one that like
minimizes um, you know, the the fee
because I know everybody hates paying
the fee. It's like when you donate to a
charity and you know they're taking a
huge lump off the top. It's just
irritating as [__] Again, it's drogram
podcast atgmail. Uh if you want to go
over to PayPal. Um I know some people
hate PayPal. Uh and if you want to So
that's much appreciated. Also, you can
do it through the YouTube and you can do
it Oh, you can do the donation through
Rumble. They don't take anything.
>> Yeah, they don't take anything at all.
>> So there that's you can definitely do
that. This was a YouTube question
though. So, uh, if you're and if you we
once we have Robbie back, he we'll bring
him back on to explain the whole desire,
uh, how why we do prefer if it's
practical for you to watch us on on
Rumble rather than YouTube just because
we get a lot higher percentage of the of
the money. Um, so thank you so much for
that. Uh,
let's see. Uh,
see, this is why we need I I need Robbie
back because I'm like so busy like going
down the scroll.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Uh anyway, so all right, we have other
stuff to talk about here. Are we done
with the shutdown? I mean, what do you
think? So, okay, what do you think is
going to happen here? I mean, is this
basic basically the beginning of the
end? Have the Democrats lost and is this
over? Are these eight traders going to
[__] us or is there some Obviously,
nothing's going to happen in the House.
Hakee Jeff aside. Um but
>> no, they're gonna cave. They're going to
cave. Um, I I tried to read
as much as I could about what exactly
this deal is, and it's it's little
stuff, Ted. First of all, it's not a
fullear budget. It's it only gets us to
January.
Um, and uh and it includes things like a
guarantee that federal workers who have
been furled will get their pay. and it
uh it reinstates everybody who was fired
by Trump over the last couple of months.
Uh and he's decimated the uh Justice
Department. So, it's little stuff. The
Democrats are agreeing to all these
little things and then they're giving up
the ACA subsidy. Just giving it up.
>> And that's the end of the ACA. And I
mean, it's going to it is going to drive
the health care system off a cliff
potentially, right? I mean, because not
only is the ACA going to collapse, cuz
it's been teetering on the edge of
disaster for years. Um, and now, you
know, the whole the whole theory behind
this stupid thing that the Heritage
Foundation came up with when it was
Romney Care was that if uh you know, it
was it was all about volume, right? How
do we do it? Volume. And so, you know,
you get a lot of people uh in this plan
and then the the the plans can negotiate
better rates with the pharmaceutical
companies and the health care companies,
blah blah blah. Um and but if you have
fewer of those people, then that's not
true anymore. And it's also uh
underpinning the private insurance
system and it's the the whole subsidies
are going to go away. Prices are going
to go up across the board, including for
people who aren't even insured.
>> Yeah, that that's right. That's right. I
told you I went from nine roughly 900 a
month to 1,900 a month and I I'm I'm not
sure how I'm going to manage this. I I
don't I can't do it. I don't have 1,900
a month for health insurance.
>> No, it's insane.
>> Yeah. I mean, right now that's more than
this show pays. So
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. That's ridiculous. Um
>> okay, so um we'll see what happens
there, obviously. All right. So, let's
talk about these part. Do you want to
talk about Nordstream or you want to
talk about the pardons?
>> Let's talk about the pardons.
>> Okay.
>> So, as you mentioned, Ted, the president
has the the legal right, the
constitutional right to pardon anybody
he wants.
>> Sure. And and there are there are
stories about Abraham Lincoln
staying up late into the night and
pardoning people by candle light. Mostly
deserters because to desert from your
army unit in the Civil War was um was a
death sentence. You were you were to be
executed for that. And he said that no
one should be should be executed for
cowardice. So he would stay awake at
night just signing pardons.
No president has pardoned as many people
in American history as Donald Trump has.
And another thing about Donald Trump is
most presidents wait until the period
[clears throat]
between an election and an inauguration.
So between early November and January
20th, we usually see a flood of pardons.
Donald Trump pardons people any time the
mood strikes him.
But the problem is many of these people,
some might even say most of these people
just aren't deserving of a pardon if you
look at
why they were convicted of a crime in
the first place. And the whole idea of a
pardon is that you've committed a crime,
you've admitted to the crime, and then
you've put your life on the right track,
and you've, you know, you've written the
ship, writed the ship. Um,
I I'd say really Rudy Giuliani doesn't
fit that category
or many of these other people.
Well, how how worthwhile is this anyway?
Right. Don't most of these people, if
they face charges, face state charges
>> in in Giuliani's case, yes.
>> So then this and so I mean I heard on uh
this morning on the radio someone
arguing that uh even a a federal pardon
is something that you can take to a
state judge and say and argue and say
these charges should be dropped because
the US government doesn't care about
them. So why should the state of
whatever care about them? Is that true?
>> In some strike me as true
>> in in some cases it is. You know, but
like with my with my state pardon that I
mentioned, Governor Terry McAuliff, I
didn't even apply for a pardon. Governor
Terry McAuliffe followed my case and
pardoned me just like that. I got this
big certificate in the mail with a gold
seal on it and the governor's signature.
It was all very ceremonial. Um, but I
hadn't committed any state crime. Still,
it was kind of a nice symbolic thing to
do. And in a lot of these cases, that's
what Trump is doing. There was no there
was no danger that Rudy Giuliani was
going to go to a federal prison. I don't
think anybody in America believed Rudy
Giuliani was eventually going to go to a
federal prison. A state prison, on the
other hand, is a real possibility, and
it continues to be a real possibility.
We should add one thing, too. I had a
long conversation with a friend of mine
last night who's not just a Republican
and a conservative, but like
irrationally Republican and conservative
where you challenge him on his beliefs
and he doesn't have any idea why he
believes these things. It's just that's
what the right says he's supposed to
believe and so he just parrots it back.
So anyway, we were talking about Elise
Defanic last night and she announced her
candidacy for governor against um Hokll
and I said I can't stand Hokll, but I'm
not a fan I'm not a fan of Elise Defanic
either. Uh I think that wherever the
wind happens to be blowing that's where
Elise Defanic is on the uh on the the
issues.
And um and he said, "Oh, Elise Defanic's
going to win." And I said, "Absolutely
not.
This year or any other year's not going
to win." And he came up with this very
complicated reason that it's going to be
on one single issue. He said,
>> um, the issue is that New Yorkers are
not allowed to carry guns. Everywhere
you go, even if you have a a gun permit,
there are signs that say no guns, no
guns, no guns, no guns. Especially
around New York City. like he said, "I
can't even carry my gun to the police
station." True.
>> Like why would you want to carry your
gun to the
>> By the way, and that's not true, right?
Ever since the what is it 2018 the
Supreme Court decision
>> Supreme Court case and I let me tell you
it's like it's not [__] there are more
signs in Kbble that say you can't carry
a gun into an establishment than there
are in New York. I mean there's no signs
on the door that say like no guns or
like a a picture of a handgun with a
with a cross through it. That's just not
true. I mean, it's guns are so off the
radar in New York City. Yeah. That
nobody bothers to ban them from their
businesses.
>> Yeah. Um
I'm responding to BIA uh real quick.
You're putting words in my mouth. Okay.
So, anyway, he said that um
he said that uh uh that New Yorkers are
so frustrated that they're going to vote
for Stfanic because they want to carry
their guns. And I said, "That is the
most ridiculous thing I've ever heard
you say, and I've heard you say some
really stupid things."
>> I agree.
>> I said, "People are going to say, "Oh,
I'm pro-choice
and I support the social safety net, but
I'm going to vote for Stfanic because
she wants me to be able to carry a gun
to a gas station."
I said, "That's seriously what you're
telling me." I said, "Listen, I'm going
to say it right now where there's plenty
of time. Elise Defanic will not be
governor of New York. Period.
>> No, there's no way. I mean, some other
Republican might possibly be. I mean,
it's not outside of the realm of
possibility. I mean, Robert Pataki was
governor of New York.
>> Sure.
>> It can happen.
>> He was a good one, too, actually. And
but I but I gotta say the population of
so in New York state right basically
roughly half the population lives in New
York City and is fervently like
left-wing Democrat and then half the
population lives everywhere else right
like we call upstate um which basically
means everything outside of New York
City. Um,
>> right.
>> And that population. So the thing is
though, the population of upstate is
like 6040 Republican. The population of
New York City and and on Verons is
probably 80% Democratic. So the So a
Democrat basically wins unless the
Democrat [__] up big time. Elise
Stefonic is not going to be the governor
of New York. Um, it's just she just
won't. Uh even if somehow it turns out
Kathy Hokll is the Eric Adams of Albany,
uh that still won't happen. Um you know,
it's it's just the demographics don't
work anymore. I'd have to say it's
almost like California. I don't think
the Republican party is viable um you
know, for statewide office in New York
anymore. It the demographics have just
changed. Um I don't think she's running
agree. The thing is, you know, the
lieutenant governor in New York um is
the person is kind of like it's very
old-fashioned. It's a separate thing,
right? the governor doesn't pick their
lieutenant governor. So, she could be
lieutenant governor easily under Hokll.
Uh, that could happen.
>> Ideologically, they're not too terribly
far apart.
>> That's true. I mean, Hokll Hokll is
trying to pivot a little bit over to the
left. She's scooching to the left um in
the wake of the Mamani win, but she's
not. She's a conservative Democrat from
Buffalo from way up on the Canadian
border.
>> That's right. I I have to admit too that
that I I think Alise Defanic got screwed
politically. She was supposed to be
ambassador of the United Nations. Trump
uh ended up taking that nomination away
from her um because he thought it would
be better for her to remain in her
congressional seat. I think she
represents Staten Island and a little
sliver of Brooklyn. Um oh, breaking
news. The Supreme Court rejects a call
to overturn its decision legalizing
same-sex marriage. There's a shock.
>> I was not surprised there. No. At all.
>> So, um,
Stfanic ended up also the Supreme Court
will decide a bunch of stuff is coming
out of the court right now. It it is
going to take a case deciding whether
mailed in mail-in ballots have to be
received by election day. They should
not. They should have to be postmarked
by election day because nobody can
control the post [clears throat] office,
right? I mean,
>> agree completely. Yes, agree completely.
So, anyway, Stfanic ended up keeping her
congressional seat. Then she had to
figure out something to do because she's
not going to be in the administration
now. And she ended up just saying,
"Well, I I'll run for governor." And I
said to him, I she's she's very
talented. She was going places in the
Republican party and um and I think her
political career is done. She can't get
elected to the Senate. She won't get
elected governor. Another Republican's
going to take her House seat. I think
she's done.
>> What is uh I mean, why is she running
for governor? I mean, why you know I I'm
I I firmly believe in the doctrine that
you should never ever pick a fight that
you cannot win.
um you know if you have a chance at
winning but there's no chance here I
mean uh okay maybe not that's an
exaggeration I think she has like a five
to one chance of be of of prevailing in
a in a gubanatorial race right I mean
that's those aren't that you don't raise
money to one
>> yeah sorry Hokll's a terrible human
being I I wouldn't lose a minute's sleep
if Hokll were to lose that that election
but I just don't think
>> I don't think that uh that she's got a
chance. [clears throat]
>> No, no way.
>> No.
>> So funny. Uh, someone said it wouldn't
be an episode of DE programmed without
an Afghanistan comparison.
>> We can't help it.
>> We can't we we we have to. Well, once
you know it's it's a you won't go I
won't go down that hole. Um, all right.
So, yeah. So, what So, okay. So, in
terms Do we want to leave the pardons
there? Oh, by the way, I do have to ask
you about Daryl Strawberry,
>> man. You know, every time I open a paper
and I see somebody's been part See,
Daryl Strawberry is another guy who
didn't even apply.
I mean, Trump loves the Mets. Daryl
Strawberry was a giant on the Mets. He
ran into some problems with taxes and
drugs and a couple of other things. He
gets [clears throat] a pardon.
Yeah. So, there it is.
>> It's Yeah. I mean, are you at the point
now like you know how that you go
through a point where you're sort of
like
>> you're you're hopeful and then like you
after a while you give up like I got to
that point applying for the Pulitzer
year after year after year and and in
all fairness I I have been a finalist
which is more than most of my peers can
say so probably shouldn't winge too much
but still yeah
>> um you know I got to the point where I I
really you know I said that I gave up
but I didn't really gave up like I sort
of crossed my fingers like but I still
kind of want it and I'm still checking.
Then I stopped paying attention to who
won and then finally I stopped applying
like where are you at in this in this uh
in in this in this cycle? Are you're
still hopeful?
>> I said I I'm I'm hopeful because if
anybody's going to pardon me, it's going
to be Donald Trump. And um but like you,
excuse [clears throat and cough] me,
like you, I'm at the point where if I
don't get it while Donald Trump is
president,
I give up.
It's going to be the end of it for me.
>> You don't think President JD Vance will
take care of it? You'll take care of
you?
>> I don't I don't think so.
>> Yeah.
All right. So, yeah. Yeah. By the way,
your friend is totally wrong about Elise
Stefonic and about guns. I mean,
>> yeah,
>> like New York City voters don't carry
guns
>> at all. I mean, you know,
>> at all.
>> And um and and like most people in the
state don't carry guns. Yeah. So,
>> that's right.
>> It's just not a I mean, I'm not even
saying they shouldn't have the right to
do it. I'm a Second Amendment person. I
just don't think that that's that's just
not going to determine the results of a
of a gubanatorial election.
>> No. And and I said to him, I said, I I
remember when I got my concealed carry
permit, um they specifically warned me
that the concealed the the multi-state
concealed carry permit is not recognized
in New York, New Jersey, or Maryland.
So, don't carry a concealed weapon in
New York, New Jersey, or Maryland. Okay,
fine.
>> I don't, by the way, the concealed the
concealed carry thing. I never
understood um like so it's like you're
allowed to carry the gun visibly but not
so I mean what what is the thinking
behind like whether society benefits
from pe from people who have who are
carrying a handgun carrying it openly
versus not openly. I I really never
understood this.
>> Yeah, that's a good question.
I I don't know to tell you the truth. I
do watch a lot of videos on Tik Tok
again last night of guys
um wearing sidearms
>> and then just standing in front of a
police station with a gimbal recording
and the cops always lose their minds and
come outside. Hey, whoa, what's going on
here? He said, just just uh practicing
my first amendment freedoms. I'm an
independent journalist working on a
story. Yeah, well, you're wearing a gun.
which is perfectly legal. And then they
always say, "You're dismissed." They say
to the cops, "You're dismissed. You can
go." Now,
>> Real Real is asking us about a Russia
story. Uh, any thoughts on the Sergey
Lavough situation? Supposedly, Putin's
second daughter is working against him.
He's been sidelined from a Security
Council meeting and is not going to the
G20.
Um yeah, that surprised me a lot
actually. Um
I told you when I was at the United
Nations, Sergey Lavrov was the Russian
ambassador and so I got to work with him
at the security council. This guy is a
very very very
impressive
uh diplomat uh better than most American
diplomats uh for whom I worked and um
but he has no political um aspirations
in Russia at all. He's he's a diplomat.
He just likes to be a diplomat
>> and he's very loyal.
>> Very intensely loyal. if if there's
something going on behind the scenes
where where he's in the process of being
sidelined, my guess is my educated guess
is that um is that he'll just retire
quietly.
>> Yeah, that I I would agree with that.
Fasmataz is asking me uh who would you
trust more? You should ask this answer
this question too, John. in their palace
at their mercy. Rasheed Dustin or God
Emperor Trump and Reich. Um, I've been
in that situation as you know if you
listen to the show. Dustin's a monster.
>> Rashid Dust.
>> Yeah, Dustin's a monster.
>> He is a monster, but he didn't lie to
me.
>> Well,
>> and and what he what he exposed to me
was that Donald Rumsfeld was an even
bigger monster.
>> Yeah. Well, that's true, too.
John is asking, "You're being asked by
uh Sud uh Sud suda, not Suda." Okay. Uh
it's very unlikely, but what if John
Brennan had the power to pardon you?
Would you accept it from him? What's the
beef between you two? I understand he's
a bad guy. The my my beef with him is
that he specifically tasked the Justice
Department with prosecuting me and then
they trumped up espionage charges which
had to be dismissed and threatened me
with 45 years in prison. It bankrupted
me. I lost friends. I lost my family. I
lost my pension. I lost my freedom. I
lost everything. That's my beef with
John Brennan. John Brennan's gonna get
what he has coming to him.
>> That's that's a big beef. John Magcguire
has a question for you. Thanks for the
10 bucks, by the way. Uh, is there
another angle you can work outside of a
pardon that would reinstate your
pension? I'm going to make this a
two-parter. We also have a question uh
like is there anything that uh from this
is from John Ward is what can we do to
help you get a pardon? Uh, in my
opinion, you should get a presidential
>> Thank you.
>> medal of freedom. Agreed.
>> Oh, thank you. Um, to answer John
Magcguire's uh question first, yeah,
there is a second angle. It's called a
writ of quorum novice. I happen to be at
a at a dinner party and I was sitting
next to a circuit court judge and we
were talking about this and I mentioned
a rit of cororum nois and she said,
"Wow." She goes, "A rit of quorumn
nobus? I haven't even heard that term
since law school. But what it is is the
Justice Department would have to go to
the Eastern District of Virginia court
and say, "We made a mistake in
prosecuting John Kuryaku. We recognize
the mistake. We admit the mistake and we
ask that his conviction be overturned."
>> They're exceedingly rare. There was one
in like 2001. There was one in 1986,
but they're very, very rare. With that
said,
you know, the Trump Justice Department
hates the legal system as much as I do,
so maybe I I stand a chance there. I
don't know. We'll see. And then what can
people do? Tell you the truth, um, an
email or a uh a letter to the US pardon
attorney, Ed Martin, would be very
helpful. Thank you.
Okay. So, um maybe we should get that
address, but just Google, right? What's
what's better, snail mail or email? I
always feel like snail mail.
>> I think snail mail is better. Um
>> so, just Google this. Just Google the
mailing address for again. Who is that
again?
>> Uh his name is Ed Martin. Here it is
right here.
>> Um you know what? I'll I'll put it in
I'll put it in the chats.
>> Okay. And I'll put it up on the on the
screen. So, Ed Martin is the u Yeah. Is
is the guy. and um you know and and try
to follow like maybe go to AI or
whatever and do formal terms of address
uh you know form of address for the
letter print it out sign it you know
yourself and drop it off with an
oldfashioned stamp in the mailbox that's
the way to go
>> thank you t
>> okay so you know that would that's maybe
that's something we should jin up here
we should like put put that up every day
and uh you know encourage people to
write because honestly if they got a
trickle of letters every day I think it
might
You know, a friend of mine called Martin
the other day. They're friends. And he
called to say, "Come on, man. You got to
pardon John Kiryaku." And Ed Martin
reportedly said, "You're the third
person today to call him about about to
call me about him. Just tell him to
relax. My his file is literally on my
desk." Is what he said. So,
>> well, that's easy to say when you're not
the one waiting for the pardon
>> to relax.
>> Yeah, that's right. Well, you know,
well, hopefully from Ed's from Ed's lips
to God's ears,
>> man. I hope so.
>> Um, all right, let's talk about
Nordstream. Um,
>> yeah.
>> So, uh, German investigators,
um, you know, they've launched this
investigation that to me, and I think
you probably agree with me, seemed like
a lot of [__] Um, basically, you
know, the this sidelines the Sai Hersh
theory of the uh US uh the US Navy uh
being involved in uh going down to the
bottom of the sea and uh to the north
the North Sea and blowing up Nordstream
back in 2022, one of the biggest acts of
eotterrorism in the history of the
world. Um anyway, uh the Germans say
that they're pointing to not really kind
of like we'd been told we'd been told
this story about the Ukrainian like
pleasure craft uh with some like random
Ukrainians uh you know out drinking a
little too much vodka going down to drop
to to blow up the pipeline. Now it look
there it's the Germans are drawing a
bead on the guy who was literally the
commander of the Ukrainian armed forces
Valeri Zalujni. Uh he's currently the
Ukrainian ambassador to London. Wall
Street Journal says the Germans are
after him and that this is causing all
sorts of rifts between Germany and
Ukraine uh between Poland and Germany
and so on. Not that Poland and Germany
have ever had any problems. Um, so the
um, so anyway, there's uh, this key guy,
Sir K, uh, who's a, uh, SBU guy. That's
the Ukra that's the Ukrainians um,
traced uh, by basically a speed camera
photo using facial recognition software.
And uh the Germans seem pretty confident
that they've got their working theory
and that their working theory is
accurate and they're ready to start uh
you know issuing subpoenas and all that.
Um what do you think? What do you make
of all this? I mean it's it's definitely
a wrinkle that I hadn't considered.
>> Yeah, this is this is kind of a crazy
development, isn't it? And it's one of
those situations, I think, where where
now
in the halls of the CIA and the
Pentagon, they just wish this thing
would go away. You know,
[snorts] the truth is not supposed to
come out in an operation like this.
Whoever did it, it the the result was
was a soop to the Ukrainians and the
West. and the Germans can't leave well
enough alone. And so I think that I
think that behind closed doors today,
there are probably calls going back and
forth to the Germans saying, "Come on,
you guys, just let this go. It's not
going to help anybody getting to the to
the bottom of the truth.
>> Why are the Germans I mean, first of
all, I guess the question is, do you
think the Germans are right?" Um, and
and I guess the other question would be
two things can both be true at the same
time, right? Maybe the Ukrainians
partnered up with the US Navy. Maybe Sih
is still right, but he only had half the
story.
>> Half the story, right? And I think
that's probably the case. Not to get too
far off the subject, but this is the
problem.
>> Yeah. This is this is the problem with
Sai is that he'll run with a story when
he has just one source.
>> And so often times he does have that
kernel of truth for the story. He just
doesn't have the details. I think this
is probably one of those cases. It very
well could have been a joint operation
which makes more sense. You'd need that
kind of expertise if you don't have it
in house.
>> Right. Right. And the thing is I mean so
what about the legal ramifications?
Right. I mean this is a act of economic
and ecological terror right in Europe.
Right. I mean so can I mean the EU has
been doing everything it can to turn a
blind eye to all this um for three
years. Yeah. But the Germans are like,
these German prosecutors are like a dog
with a bone and they're not letting it
go. Um, you know, where do I mean they
at this point they can't let it go. So,
what next?
>> Well, I think that I think that we're
going to see people prosecuted. I think
that especially this um this Ukrainian
uh this Ukrainian military person that
the uh that the Wall Street Journal is
reporting on uh they're saying that he's
going to be in the dock soon. He's going
to be forced to testify whether he likes
it or not. And I think I think somebody
probably this guy uh is going to go to
prison.
>> Really?
>> I do.
>> Even former commander of the Ukrainian
armed forces. I mean, he was the he's
the Coen Powell of
>> Yeah, he's the Coen Powell. But, I mean,
he's a nobody now. It's all over for for
him.
>> Um, we have some breaking news coming
out of India. There's been a car bombing
>> uh in uh New Delhi uh outside of the Red
Fort tourist attraction. If you've ever
been there to New
>> Delhi, there there are more than two
dozen uh injured so far. I haven't seen
any number on on deaths, but it's
clearly a terrorist attack. the the
pictures and video from the Red Fort
this morning are are grizzly.
>> Care to speculate?
>> You know, I wouldn't be at all surprised
if it was Kashmir separatist groups.
Again, I'm going to get death threats
from Pakistanis now like I did two or
three weeks ago when I say that that
that these groups carry out terrorist
attacks. Yeah, they carry out terrorist
attacks because they're terrorist
groups. Whatever your political point is
is irrelevant. If you're out there
murdering civilians, you're a terrorist.
>> That's terrorism. Yeah. For political
purposes. That's the definition.
>> Political. That's the definition of
terrorism. So yeah, I I would I would
bet this is probably Kashmir's.
>> Well, we'll follow all these stories uh
coming up tomorrow. Um as I said, we're
here Monday through Friday, 9:00 a.m.
Eastern time. We'll be back tomorrow
even though it's Veterans Day. Uh so
please ch uh catch up with us then.
Please like, follow, and share the show
whether you're watching live or you're
watching on streaming. We really
appreciate you. We are back fully funded
on YouTube. And uh, of course, we were
never dropped off Rumble, but we really
appreciate your support over there. Uh,
if you want to donate um to the show uh
without getting dinged for a service
fee, uh, please do it over on Rumble.
And, uh, we'll have Robbie back next
week. Thank you again if you're joining
us on the late side. We made our
thousand goal for the month of November.
You will not be hearing from us begging
for money for Robbie aid uh for the rest
of the month. So, thank you so much for
coming through. Uh you'll I'm going to
be here starting up in just about 30
>> [music]
[music]